Baby
宝宝宝宝
Bus bike riding
骑自行车的婴儿巴士
lesson
课课课
wow yooo hey W
哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇
aome Hey Brother Robin do you know how
嘿 Robin兄弟 你知道如何
to ride a
嘿 Robin兄弟 你知道怎么骑
bike riding a bike is
骑自行车
easy watch this
骑自行车很容易看这个
简单看这个
easy watch this
brother rabbit are you
兔子兄弟,你是谁啊?
okay I'm fine I'll figure it out
没事,我没事,我会想出办法的
soon let's do it
没事,我没事,我很快会想出办法的 我们开始吧
I want to quit it's too hard
我想退出,这太难了
stop watch
我想戒掉,这太难收手表了
out stop you'll never catch
在外面停停,你永远抓不到
me can I borrow your bike sure
我能借你的自行车借我用一下吗?
wow wolf you can't get
哇,狼啊,你无法得到
away stop right
停止右转
there I turn
站住,我转弯
我转过去转过去
there I turn
it stop
停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停
breathing W you're coming with us
停止呼吸 你跟我们走
wow you guys are awesome thanks for the
哇,你们真是太棒了 感谢你们
bike it really helped us a
哇,你们这些家伙真棒 感谢的自行车 它真的帮了我们一个
骑自行车真的帮了我们
bike it really helped us a
lot oh you're
骑自行车真的帮了我们很多
呵呵,你,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,你
lot oh you're
hurt I want to ride a bike but I keep
我想骑自行车,但是我一直想骑自行车
falling over do you still want to learn
受伤了,我想骑自行车 但我一直掉倒在地上,你还想学吗?
你还想学吗?
falling over do you still want to learn
uhhuh no falling hurts so much don't
你还想学吗? 没有摔倒伤的伤痛吗?
嗯,没有跌落伤害这么多 如此多 不要
uhhuh no falling hurts so much don't
worry we'll teach you
嗯,不跌不跌伤这么多 别担心,我们会教你的
担心我们会教你
worry we'll teach you
first find a safe flat area with few
担心我们会教你先找到一个安全的地方
首先找到一个安全公寓区,只有很少的
first find a safe flat area with few
people then put on your safety
先找一个安全公寓区,人少 然后再安身
here
在这里
yeah adjust the seat to the right
在这里,是的 调整座位到右边
# 将座位调整到右边 #
yeah adjust the seat to the right
height so your feet can touch the ground
# 将座位调整到正确的高度, 这样你的脚可以触摸到地面 #
高高高高高高的脚能触摸地面
height so your feet can touch the ground
see it's less scary now right uhhuh try
让你的脚能触摸到地面 这样就不那么可怕了
看吧,现在不那么可怕了 试试吧
see it's less scary now right uhhuh try
scooting with your feet to find some
现在不那么可怕了 试着用脚踩脚 找一些
脚踩踏踏脚寻找一些
scooting with your feet to find some
balance
脚踏脚踏足寻找平衡
结余
balance
good job just like that keep your eyes
干得漂亮 保持你的眼睛
on the
好工作 就像那样 保持你的眼睛
会 议 日 程 和 议 程
on the
road there's a big rock what do I do huh
路上有块大石头,我该怎么办?
路边有块大石头,我该怎么办呢?
road there's a big rock what do I do huh
where where where's the big
路边有块大石头,我该怎么办? 哪里有大石头?
哪里是大号在哪里?
where where where's the big
rock right
哪里是大石头的右边
here is this the big
这是这里最大的
rock now let's practice breaking and
这就是这个大石头 让我们来练习一下破碎
现在让我们练习一下破碎和
rock now let's practice breaking and
turning okay
现在让我们练习一下 打破和转好
I'm going to hit the train Don't Panic
我要上火车了,不要惊慌
try breaking
我要上火车了,别惊慌,别乱撞
gently great be careful slow
慢慢慢慢慢慢小心
down riding is so hard I want to quit
下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下下
wow that's cool I almost gave up
哇,这很酷,我差点放弃
learning to ride a bike as a
哇,这很酷,我差点放弃 学习学骑自行车作为一个
学习如何骑自行车
learning to ride a bike as a
kid then how did you
小时候学会骑自行车,然后你是怎么做到的?
小子,那你怎样?
kid then how did you
learn
小子,那你是怎么学的?
学习学习
learn
well watch
看好看好
out no Doby
没有多比
oh I fell again Mommy I want to
哦,我又摔倒了 妈妈,我想
quit it's okay
哦,我又摔倒了,妈妈,我想退出,没关系
戒了,没事的
quit it's okay
honey if you fall get back up and you'll
戒酒没关系蜂蜜 如果你摔倒了 爬起来,你会的
蜂蜜,如果你掉下来 爬起来,你会
honey if you fall get back up and you'll
soon be able to do it okay and finally
蜂蜜,如果你掉下来了 回来,你会很快 能够做到这一点好,最后
很快就能做好 最终顺利完成
soon be able to do it okay and finally
here I
很快就能完成 最终我终于在这里
这里I
here I
am if you fall don't get back up that's
如果你摔倒了,我在这里 不爬不起来,这是
如果你摔倒了,不 得到备份
am if you fall don't get back up that's
it don't be afraid to fall don't give up
如果你摔倒了,不要爬起来... ...不要害怕摔倒... ...不要放弃,不要放弃,不要放弃
不要放弃,不要害怕摔倒,不要放弃
it don't be afraid to fall don't give up
when it's hard okay I'll keep
不怕摔倒 很难的时候不要放弃
困难的时候我会留下
when it's hard okay I'll keep
trying come on great keep it
当困难的时候,我会继续尝试 来伟大的,保持它
来来来来来来来来来来来来来来,好好保存它
trying come on great keep it
up a big rock a big rock don't worry
来,加油,加油,保持它 一个大石头 一个大石头 别担心,一个大石头 不用担心,一个大石头
一块大石头 一块大石头 不用担心
up a big rock a big rock don't worry
can't
一个大石头 一个大石头 不用担心
break it really is a big
折断它真的很大
rock keep your balance slowly turn
打破它真的是一个巨大的岩石 保持你的平衡 慢慢的转动
that's
这是
it
就是这样
good good job keep
良好的工作 保持良好的工作
going don't be scared steady you can do
不要害怕,稳稳的,你可以做到
it
不要害怕,稳稳的,你能做到的
woohoo
呼呼呼呼呼呼
wow I know how to ride a
哇哇哇哇 我知道如何骑
bike brother Robin there's no good cool
{\fn黑体\fs22\bord1\shad0\3aHBE\4aH00\fscx67\fscy66\2骑自行车的Robin兄弟 没有酷酷的
you did
{\fn黑体\fs22\bord1\shad0\3aHBE\4aH00\fscx67\fscy66\2自行车哥哥Robin Robin 你没有那么酷
您确实
you did
great almost better than me thank you
你比我做得好多了 谢谢你
比我好多了,谢谢你
great almost better than me thank you
for teaching me but it was your effort
几乎比我还好 谢谢你教我 但这是你的努力
教教我,但那是你的努力
for teaching me but it was your effort
that mattered most
教教我,但最要紧的是你的努力
rabbit let's go for a ride okay
兔子,我们去兜兜兜风,好吗?
bye-bye
兔子,我们去兜兜风吧,再见
再见
bye-bye
bye Sheriff's not things to keep in
拜拜拜 警长的 东西没有 保持了
永别了 警长的不是东西 保持在
bye Sheriff's not things to keep in
mind kids it's normal to fall when
想着孩子们 摔倒是正常的 当
learning how to ride a bike don't be
当孩子们在学习骑自行车时 通常会摔倒
学会骑自行车
learning how to ride a bike don't be
scared and don't give up if you fall get
学会如何骑自行车 不要害怕,不放弃,如果你摔倒了。
如果你跌倒了,害怕,不放弃,不放弃
scared and don't give up if you fall get
back up and keep trying you'll learn for
害怕不放弃,不放弃 如果你摔倒了 站起来,继续尝试 你会学习
继续努力学习
back up and keep trying you'll learn for
sure always wear your safety gear and
继续努力学习 一定要始终穿着安全装备
一定要始终佩戴安全装备,
sure always wear your safety gear and
practice in a safe place with your
一定要佩戴安全装备 并在安全的地方练习
parents we'll be cheering you
家长们 我们会为你们欢呼
on don't stay up
千万别熬夜不眠
late Doby you need to wake up early
迟到的多比 你需要早早醒来
tomorrow go to
迟到的多比,你明天要早早醒来 去
bed sh oh already asleep good
已经睡得睡得很好
night she can't nag me now I can keep
夜夜她不能烦我 现在我可以留着了
watching
深夜她不能烦我 现在我可以一直看着了
TV Doby wake
电视《多比守夜》
up oh no I overslept
哦,不,我睡过头了
I'm late I'm
我迟到了,我迟到了,我迟到了
late eat
晚食
breakfast wow smells so
早饭吃晚 闻起来好香
早餐,哇,闻起来好香
breakfast wow smells so
good but no time to eat I'm going to be
早餐闻起来好香 好香,但没时间吃饭,我要去
late sorry I'm
对不起,对不起,我
late where is everyone are they late
对不起,我迟到了,谁都迟到了?
人到哪里都迟到? 晚到? 晚到? 晚到? 晚到? 晚到?
late where is everyone are they late
too Doby
多比,谁都迟到,谁都迟到,多比
多比
too Doby
we've been waiting why didn't you answer
我们等了很久,为什么你不回答?
我们等了很久,你为什么不回答
we've been waiting why didn't you answer
your phone huh
我们一直在等 为什么你不接电话?
phone I took the remote instead of my
我用遥控器代替了我的电话
phone get in it's time to patrol
我用遥控器代替手机 进去巡逻的时候到了
打电话去巡逻的时候到了
phone get in it's time to patrol
okay oh dear we won't make it there on
亲爱的 我们到不了那里了
time it's all my fault because I woke up
亲爱的,哦,亲爱的,我们不会及时赶到那里 都是我的错,因为我醒了
都是我的错,因为我醒了
time it's all my fault because I woke up
late
都是我的错,因为我醒晚了
that car has a flat tire go check it
车胎爆胎了,去查一查
out oh no what should we do we're
哦,不,不,我们该做什么
running late is everything okay our tire
哦,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不
迟到是一切正常 我们的轮胎
running late is everything okay our tire
blew out my class is going to the ice
迟到是一切顺利 我们的轮胎炸掉 我的课要到冰冰了
炸掉我的班级 要去冰雪
blew out my class is going to the ice
castle today but now I can't
炸掉我的课 今天要去冰城堡,但现在我不能
今天城堡,但现在我不能
castle today but now I can't
go oh little rabbit don't worry we'll
今天城堡,但现在我不能去哦 小兔子别担心我们会去
哦,小兔子,别担心,我们会的
go oh little rabbit don't worry we'll
take you there huh really miss rabbit
哦 小兔子别担心 我们会带你去那儿的 真的很想念兔子
把你带到那里,哈哈,真怀念兔子
take you there huh really miss rabbit
I'll help you fix the
带你去那儿吧 真的很想念兔子 我会帮你修好的
我帮你修补
I'll help you fix the
tire thank you so
我帮你修轮胎,谢谢
much buckle up kid we're
系好安全带,孩子,我们是
off you
离开你
tired I stayed up late last
你累了吗? 上次我熬夜到很晚
night and had no time for breakfast
夜间没有时间吃早餐,
either huh what's wrong with that car
晚上没有时间吃早餐 也没有时间吃早餐 那辆车怎么了?
ouch my fish
摸我的鱼
finally done sorry I nodded off for a
对不起,我终于做了 对不起,我点了点头
moment drowsy driving is dangerous
对不起,我终于做了 对不起,我点头了 有一瞬间昏昏沉沉的驾驶很危险
昏昏沉沉的驾驶很危险
moment drowsy driving is dangerous
you'll be in trouble remember safety
昏昏欲睡的驾驶很危险 你会有麻烦的 记住安全
你会有麻烦的 记住安全
you'll be in trouble remember safety
first
你会有麻烦的 记得安全,先记住安全
第一次
first
okay we can finally get going can we
我们终于可以出发了 我们能
好了,我们终于可以出发了,可以吗?
okay we can finally get going can we
make it in time don't worry I know a
我们终于可以出发了 我们能及时赶到 不用担心 我知道
不要担心,我知道一个
make it in time don't worry I know a
shortcut to the ice castle we'll make it
不要担心 我知道一条通往冰城堡的捷径 我们会成功的
通往冰城堡的捷径 我们会成功的
shortcut to the ice castle we'll make it
once we cross the bridge we'll be there
一旦我们过桥 我们就会在那里
soon the bridge is
桥快桥快桥了
broken oh no what do we do now no
哦,不,不,我们该怎么办,我们现在做什么
worries Hold On
哦,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不
担心 继续
worries Hold On
Tight w
紧 紧
hey T feel added a new sled
嘿 T感觉又加了一辆新雪橇
mode wow this is
嘿 T感觉又加了一个新的雪橇模式 哇,这是
cool look it's the ice castle Hang on
酷酷,看,这是冰城堡 挂挂
we're speeding up
酷酷,看,这是冰城堡 挂挂,我们正在加速
ice castle here I
这里的冰雪城堡
come where are mischief and
火狱有恶报,
others they must be
其他人必须
inside I'm too
其他人肯定在里面 我也在里面
我也在内心深处
inside I'm too
late line up everyone we're starting to
排排排排排排排排排 每个人,我们开始
explore the ice castle little rabbit
我们开始探索冰城堡的小兔子
探索冰城堡的小兔子
explore the ice castle little rabbit
look over
探索冰城堡的小兔子 望过
向下看一看
look over
there this sheep and my friends oh
看那边,这只羊和我的朋友哦
还有这只羊和我的朋友哦
there this sheep and my friends oh
little rabbit come join
这儿有只羊和我的朋友 哦 小兔子一起来
小兔子来加入
little rabbit come join
us hey thank you so much I won't stay up
小兔子来加入我们吧 嘿 非常感谢你,我不会熬夜的
非常感谢你,我不会熬夜不睡
us hey thank you so much I won't stay up
late at
非常感谢你们,我不会熬夜
晚到时间
late at
night little rabbit you made it
小小兔子,你做了它
mining Mom oh you're up pretty early and
矿工妈妈哦 你起得挺早的
look energetic
矿工妈妈哦 你起得还早着 看上去很活跃
看起来很有活力
look energetic
too I went to bed early last
外表也挺有活力 上次我早早早睡的
上次也早早睡了,也早早睡了
too I went to bed early last
night so
我昨天晚上也早早睡了,所以...
夜夜如此如此
night so
delicious Sheriff's notes things to keep
美味的警长的笔记 保存的东西
in
美味的警长的笔记 保存在
内
in
mind kids it's very important not to to
记住孩子们,重要的是不要
记住孩子们,这是非常重要的,不要
mind kids it's very important not to to
stay up late getting enough sleep is
孩子们别介意 不要熬夜睡得睡得够久是很重要的
熬夜睡得睡得睡得够久
stay up late getting enough sleep is
like filling up your body with fuel
熬夜睡得睡得睡得睡得睡得睡得睡得睡得着 就像用燃料充满你的身体一样
就像用燃料填充身体一样
like filling up your body with fuel
making you feel great the next day good
就像用燃料充满你的身体 让你第二天感觉棒极了
隔天你就会感觉棒极了
making you feel great the next day good
sleep habits will help you stay healthy
第二天良好的睡眠习惯会帮助你保持健康
睡觉习惯有助于保持健康
sleep habits will help you stay healthy
and strong please remember
睡习惯会帮助你保持健康和健康,请记住
坚固的、坚固的、
and strong please remember
that police versus hungry
警察对饥饿
worm I lost again one more time
我又输了一次,又输一次
hting turn it off let's get ready to go
把它关掉,我们准备出发吧
to the
把它关掉,让我们准备好去
会 议 日 和 排
to the
beach come on let's go I'm not going I'm
海滩 来 来 我们走 我不走 我不走
沙滩,来吧,我们走吧 我不去,我不去
beach come on let's go I'm not going I'm
going to keep playing
沙滩上来吧,我们走吧,我不走,我不走 我要继续玩
继续播放
going to keep playing
okay
还好
wo the hungry
饿着饿着饿着饿着饿着饿着饿着饿着饿着
worm awesome you're hungry aren't you
线虫真棒,你饿了,你饿了,不是吗?
here have some of my
线虫,真棒,你饿了,你饿了 你在这里是不是有我的一些
来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来 来来来来来来来来来来
here have some of my
snacks there for
这里有一些我的零食 在那里为
那边的零点点心
snacks there for
you w just like in the game eating a lot
为你准备的零零食 喜欢在游戏中吃很多东西
你只是喜欢在游戏中吃很多东西
you w just like in the game eating a lot
and getting
你只是喜欢在游戏中 吃了很多,得到
bigger no more
不再有大
Snacks still
再没有大点的草纸了
草纸还是
Snacks still
hungry look I don't have anymore
草纸还饿着呢 看上去我已经没有了
肚子饿的表情,我不再有
hungry look I don't have anymore
you can't eat
不能吃东西
that no not those
你不能吃,不吃,不吃,不吃,不吃,不吃
这等人,绝不是否认的,
that no not those
iner all set to
内置全部设置为
go like the sound
Iner 全部设置就绪, 和声音一样
it's the hungry word from the game it's
这是游戏中饥饿的字词
not going to eat us is
这是游戏中饥饿的字词 它不会吃我们
不吃我们就是
not going to eat us is
it I'm not afraid of
我不怕吃我们,因为我不怕
you
您 您 的 您 您
oops yes my robot arms and backpack
是的,我的机械手和背包
everyone
每个人,每 人, 每 人, 每 人, 每 人, 每 人, 每 人
F
每个人 F
hurry oh no it's ate the car
哦,快点啊,不,它吃了车
it ate the bus
哦,快点啊,不,它吃了车 它吃了公交车
它吃了巴士
it ate the bus
too
车也吃,车也吃
goodness your ice cream thanks run
天啊,你的冰淇淋 感谢跑
everyone
冰淇淇淋,谢谢大家快跑
come
来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来
on I can't run
我跑不动,跑不动
anymore pudding how can we end this
我不能再跑布丁了 我们怎么才能结束这一切
布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布布
anymore pudding how can we end this
hungry Worm
布丁,我们怎么才能结束这个饥饿的虫子呢?
饥饿的虫子
hungry Worm
Game it disappears when it bites its own
当它咬自己时,它就会消失
body oh
躯体哦
oh I have an idea let's lead it into the
哦,我有一个想法,让我们 引导它进入
maze so it'll bump into
哦,我有个主意,让我们把它带进迷宫,这样它会撞到
迷宫,所以它会撞上
maze so it'll bump into
itself hey hungry worm we're
我们饿着
here come on come on come and get me
来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来
hey word I'm
嘿的单词我
here look over here
看这里,看这里
a we're almost
a 我们几乎
there get out of the
离开那里
way Pap Doby Sheriff lavador
Pap Doby 警长厕所
it was just a
这只是一个
dream packed and ready to go all packed
这只是一个梦想 包装,准备去所有包装
做梦都打包好 准备全部打包好
dream packed and ready to go all packed
py are you really not going with
梦想打包好,准备去 所有打包的皮皮,你真的没有去
皮皮,你真的不 与
py are you really not going with
us you're still here wait for me I'm
我们你们还在这里等我
going with you guys
我们你们还在这里等我,我跟你们一起去
和你们一起去
going with you guys
no more games being with you guys is
不要再跟你们玩游戏了
much better than any
没有更多的游戏 和你们在一起比任何游戏都好
比任何比任何都好
much better than any
game what are we waiting
比任何游戏都好 我们等待什么
我们在等待什么游戏
game what are we waiting
for let's go yeah
我们在等什么,我们走吧
shrinking
正在缩小
beam what big S
光束这么大S
doing
业 业 业 业 业 业
wow it's done the shrinking beam I'm
哇,我的光束收缩了
going to try it on this toy car
哇,它完成了不断缩小的光束 我要试一下这个玩具车
试试看这辆玩具车
going to try it on this toy car
first yay it worked time to make it big
首先,它工作的时间 使它变大
again it got even
连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连 连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连连
smaller what went
它再次变小了,甚至更小 什么去了
变小的
smaller what went
wrong H I know I'm missing a part I'll
小一点,小一点,小一点,错一点 H,我知道我错过了一部分,我会的
错了H 我知道我错过了一部分 我会的
wrong H I know I'm missing a part I'll
go get it
错了H,我知道我错过了 一部分,我去拿
pudding why did you make such a mess it
布布丁,你为什么把布布丁弄得这么乱
wasn't me it was
布布丁,你为什么弄得这么乱 为什么不是我?
ping stop throwing food around invites
停止乱扔食物
roaches and ants you too clean it
停止扔食物 周围的蟑螂和蚂蚁,你太干净了。
蟑螂和蚂蚁 你太干净了
roaches and ants you too clean it
up I'll check it when I get back okay
蟑螂和蚂蚁,你太 清理它了起来,我会检查它 当我回来,好吗?
上上去,我回来再检查一下,好吗?
up I'll check it when I get back okay
she's always
我回来后会检查的,没事的,她总是
nagging the last cake is mine but that's
最后的蛋糕是我做的,但那是
mine wow give me the cake
把我的蛋糕给我
what's going
发生什么事了
on the pencil is so big ouch the book is
铅笔上发生的一切 如此之大 触摸着书本
在铅笔上是如此大 触摸着书
on the pencil is so big ouch the book is
huge too wo the cabinet is so
在铅笔上是如此大 触摸着书本是如此之大 内阁如此如此如此
内阁太庞大了 内阁如此
huge too wo the cabinet is so
tall no we got
内阁太高高了 我们没有
Shunk what do we do let's look
我们该做什么? 让我们看看吧?
around wow
哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇
周围哇
around wow
look it's such a big cake we can share
哇,你看,这是这样一个大蛋糕 我们可以分享
看样子这蛋糕这么大,我们可以一起吃
look it's such a big cake we can share
it yay
看样子蛋糕这么大,我们可以一起吃
呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀
it yay
awesome a giant
巨人 巨人 巨人 巨人 巨人 巨人 巨人 巨人 巨人 巨人 巨人 巨人 巨人 巨人 巨人 巨人 巨人 巨人
cockroach over there it's a toy car get
那边有蟑螂,是玩具车
in
那边有蟑螂,是玩具车,上车
内
in
oh no oh no way out no way here
哦,不,不,哦,没有出路 没有办法在这里
either it's flying over
要么飞过去 要么飞过去
hurry
快点
yay w
a it's Pizza Quick
是披萨快快快
hide it's gone that was
藏起来了
scary are you trembling now no I'm not
藏起来了,你现在颤抖得可怕吗? 不,我不是
你现在在发抖吗? 不,我不是
scary are you trembling now no I'm not
why is the pizza Ming
吓得你现在发抖了吗? 不,我不是为什么是披萨明
为什么披萨明
why is the pizza Ming
W so many ants
为什么披萨明W这么多蚂蚁
太多蚂蚁
W so many ants
run I'm St it was you you little
这么多蚂蚁跑来跑来跑去,我叫斯特 是你,你这个小
跑,我叫St,是你,你个小
run I'm St it was you you little
jelly no don't take us
跑啊,我叫St,是你,你这个小果冻... 不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不
away did you finish cleaning
你清扫完没有?
up so many
你打扫了这么多东西吗?
挂起如此多
up so many
ants big sister
好多蚂蚁,大姐姐
help ping H where are
帮助 ping H 在哪里
you oh we're here oh no she can't hear
哦,我们在这里 哦,不,她听不到
哦,我们在这里 哦,不,她听不见
you oh we're here oh no she can't hear
us Hy
哦,我们在这里 哦,不,不,她听不见我们,阿海
我们阿海
us Hy
he the shrinking theme is on did they
我们阿海,他这个越来越小的主题 是在他们身上吗?
他正在收缩的主题 是否他们
he the shrinking theme is on did they
get
正在收缩的主题 是否他们得到
shrunk could the ants have taken
蚂蚁可能已经收缩了
them help we're here this way I
蚂蚁们可能已经把他们带走了 帮我们找到这里
帮他们帮忙,我们在这里这样,我
them help we're here this way I
think please we don't want to be eaten
帮他们帮我们到这里 我想请不要吃东西
请你别以为我们不想被吃掉
think please we don't want to be eaten
by ant I can't find
以为我们不想被我找不到的蚂蚁吃掉
我找不到蚂蚁
by ant I can't find
them help
我找不到他们的帮助
is we're alive
我们还活着吗?
huh big
我们还活着吗? 很大啊
HH 重
huh big
sister finally found
姐姐终于找到了
you so big
你这么大
we're back to
我们又回到
normal ants and cockroaches are so
我们又回到了正常的蚂蚁和蟑螂
正常的蚂蚁和蟑螂
normal ants and cockroaches are so
scary so what should you do
正常的蚂蚁和蟑螂都吓得吓得要死
next developing good habits not throwing
下一个发展好习惯,不扔
food and keeping the room
接下来发展好习惯,不扔食物,不留房间
并留居室内;
food and keeping the room
clean be careful of
清洁的,当当心,
termites down back in our cabin Mr so
我们小屋的白蚁 苏先生
much
多
yay my favorite Rocky
我最喜欢的洛基
horse oh be careful
哦,小心马马哦,哦,小心
a what's going
(a) 正在发生的事情
on huh oh
发生什么事了啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊
my let's get out of here
我们离开这儿吧
woof hi Sheriff Lor house there's
{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3cH2F2F2F
something scary in my
洛尔警长家有可怕的东西在我
house hello hello let's hurry
哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈 快点快点
over what happened to this
这件事的经过,
door Mr rabbit help down
这扇门发生的事 兔子先生帮下忙
兔子先生帮下忙
door Mr rabbit help down
here let's pull them
兔子先生来帮忙,我们拉拉
up Sheriff Labrador there's something
拉布拉多警长有件事
scary in the house look my house is all
拉布拉多警长 房子里有些恐怖的东西
家里可怕的恐怖 看着,我的房子是全部
scary in the house look my house is all
messed up Mr rabbit you guys go to a
房子吓坏了,看,我的 房子是全搞砸了 兔子先生 你们去
搞乱了兔子先生 你们去
messed up Mr rabbit you guys go to a
safe place we've got
你们去一个安全的地方吧
安全的地方,我们有
safe place we've got
this all the wood is damaged
所有木柴都损坏了
but the metal parts are
所有木柴都损坏了 但金属零件都被损坏了
okay who's playing tricks on us come
谁在耍我们? 谁在耍我们? 谁在耍我们? 谁在耍我们?
out Doby are you all
外面的多比是你们所有的人
right I'm
对,对,对,我
fine huh
没事,我很好,是吧?
经济、社会、经济、 经济、社会、
fine huh
listen inside the
听在内心
wall oh I saw something papion use your
哦,我看见有什么东西Papion 利用你的
device huh watch this super mini
哦,我看见有什么东西Papion 使用你的设备, 呵呵看着这个超级迷你。
注意这个超级迷你
device huh watch this super mini
detection robot swee
注意这个超级迷你探测器
机器人wewee
detection robot swee
Tada nothing
机器人wee Tada 什么都没有
# 什么都没有 # # # 什么都没有 # # # # 什么都没有 # # # # # # 什么都没有 # # # # # # # # # # 什么都没有 # # # # # # # # #
Tada nothing
here what where's speee
这里什么是Speee
huh huh
这里什么是Speee啊哈哈哈哈哈
huh
中、英、法、俄、西
TW tweet tweet there you are Tweety
TW TW 微微微微微微微微微的微微微的微微微微的微微微微微的微微微微微的微微微微的微微微微微的微微微微的微微微的微微微的微微微的微微微的微微微的微微微的微微微的微微微微的微微的微微微的微微微微的微微微的微微微微的微微微微的微微微微微微的微微微微微的微微微微微微微微微的微微微微微微微的微微微微微微微微微微的微微微微微的微微微微微的微微微微
tweet tweet get going
TW推特推特,你就是TweetyTwitter推特 开始吧
Twitter推文继续
tweet tweet get going
tweee TW
推特推特推文 开始TWT
tweee TW 千兆瓦
tweee TW
TW twet twet
TW 特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿特湿
TW
TW 千瓦
TW the inside of the wall has been eaten
墙里面被吃掉了
away there's something over
墙的内墙被吃掉了 上面有东西
外面有东西过去
away there's something over
there Tweety follow it tweet
那边有东西在那边 特威提跟着推特
TW twet TW
TW 湿湿TW
huh where did it
(a) 国家、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、
go there it is over there here too
到那边去,那边也在这里
that's a lot Tweety zoom in tweet
在那里,它也在这里 这里,这是很多Tweety 缩放在推文中
这在推特上实在是太微小了
that's a lot Tweety zoom in tweet
twet ah termites they love to munch on
他们喜欢吃白蚁
wood no wonder all the furniture is
怪不得所有的家具都是
难怪所有的家具都是
wood no wonder all the furniture is
ruined tweet tweet
难怪所有的家具都毁了推特推文
被摧毁的推特推文
ruined tweet tweet
what's this the termite Queen oh no
这是什么 白蚁女王哦不
soldier termites are with the
这是什么 白蚁女王哦 没有士兵白蚁与
士兵的白蚁与
soldier termites are with the
queen Tweety run creep they are flying
士兵的白蚁和皇后 特威蒂 跑步的爬虫在一起 他们飞起来了
他们飞着飞着跑着跑来跑去
queen Tweety run creep they are flying
through my
皇后Tweety跑步的爬虫 他们飞过我的
suit creepy watch this activating flight
西装令人毛骨悚然 观看这个启动飞行的飞行
mode TW
模式 TW
Tre
特雷
treat Tweety good
优待优待
job what's
工作是什么
happening the termites are coming out
白蚁们忽然露出白蚁,
what y
是什么 y
watch out let's go
小心点,我们走吧
outside there are too many of
外外有太多的
them through the
外边有太多的动物,
window why so many termites look go
窗口中,为什么有这么多的 白蚁外观 go
your house is damaged by termites what
你们的房屋,被白蚁所破坏的,
do we do now you need professionals to
你的房子被白蚁损坏了 我们现在该做什么? 你需要专业的专业人员
现在,我们需要你需要专业的专业人员
do we do now you need professionals to
deal with
需要专业人士来应付
处理
deal with
them leave the termites to us let's
将白蚁留给我们,让我们把白蚁留给他们吧!
go termites can damage wood if your
白白蚁可以破坏木木,如果
house is empty make sure to keep it
白蚁可以破坏木头 如果你的房子是空的 确保保持它
房屋是空的, 一定要保存它
house is empty make sure to keep it
aired out and try to keep termites away
房子是空的,一定要保持空气 并尽量保持白蚁远离
喷出空气,试图远离白蚁
aired out and try to keep termites away
okay will will
吐出空气,尽量不让白蚁离开,好吗?
Sheriff labrador's safety
拉布拉多警长的安全
talk kids termites are bugs that like to
拉布拉多警长的安全谈话 小孩白蚁就是喜欢的虫子
闲聊孩子的白蚁是喜欢的虫子
talk kids termites are bugs that like to
eat
闲聊孩子的白蚁就是喜欢吃吃的虫子
食 食 食 食
eat
wood they chew on wooden furniture and
他们吃木头,他们吃木头,他们吃木木头,
以木制和木制,为他们所嚼的木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木木木木木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木制木
wood they chew on wooden furniture and
buildings if you find termites in your
他们以木木的木的木的木的木的木的和木的木的木的木的,如果你们发现有白蚁,
如果在你的建筑里发现白蚁,
buildings if you find termites in your
house tell your parents to deal with
如果你在家中发现白蚁,请父母处理。
them lie detector hat
他们的测谎帽
wow happy
哇 高兴
birthday want to have some cake yay
生日要吃蛋糕耶
cake wow such a beautiful
蛋糕啊 哇哇 如此美丽
cake what happened why is the cake empty
为什么蛋糕是空的?
inside who did this to my cake
发生什么了 为什么蛋糕里面是空的 是谁把我的蛋糕弄成这样
let's go check
我们去查一查
okay is everything all
我们去查一查,没事就是一切
都还好就是一切
okay is everything all
right sh
一切都还好,没事的 shsh
权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利 权利
right sh
labador someone ruined the birthday cake
有人毁了生日蛋糕
I prepared for my
有人毁了我准备的生日蛋糕
daughter a big piece is
女儿,一个大块是
missing bite marks someone snuck in and
女儿的一块大块是 缺少咬痕 有人溜进来,
失踪的咬痕 某人偷偷溜进来
missing bite marks someone snuck in and
ate a junk
有人偷偷溜进去吃垃圾
吃垃圾
ate a junk
what sir there's no sign of anyone
先生,没有任何人的踪迹
先生,没有任何人的踪影
what sir there's no sign of anyone
coming in
先生,没有任何人进来的踪影
进来
coming in
then someone inside the house ate the
然后有人进来 房子里面有人吃了
然后有人在屋子里吃了
then someone inside the house ate the
cake no it wasn't me H someone must be
然后家里有人吃了蛋糕 不,不是我,一定有人吃了蛋糕
没有蛋糕蛋糕,没有蛋糕,它不是我 不是我 H一定有人
cake no it wasn't me H someone must be
lying I think we need a lie detector
肯定有人在撒谎 我想我们需要测谎仪
我认为我们需要一个测谎仪
lying I think we need a lie detector
Pap Pap always has a way look the light
我认为我们需要一个测谎器 Pap Pap 总是有办法看着光线
帕帕帕总是有办法 看着光线
Pap Pap always has a way look the light
detector hat it can tell what's true or
Pap Pap总能看透光探测器的帽子 它能分辨出什么是真实的
它能分辨什么是真实的 或
detector hat it can tell what's true or
a
它能分辨什么是真实的 或什么是真实的
a a/
a
lie
谎言
wow Doby you go
撒了谎啊 多比 你走吧
哇,你走了
wow Doby you go
first Doby are you hiding snacks in in
哇,多比,你先走 多比,你把零点心藏在
首先多比,你把零点心藏在里面
first Doby are you hiding snacks in in
your pockets what no
多比先是把零食藏在口袋里
口袋里有什么没有
your pockets what no
no fly
口袋里没有苍蝇
无飞
no fly
fly
无苍蝇
huh
中、英、法、俄、西
wo that tles all right all right I lied
我撒谎了,我撒谎了
no please
我撒谎了,不,求你了
stop pH this one is really
停止PH这个真的
something who's
停止PH这个 是一个真正的东西是谁
next how about you little
接下来你这个小矮小的
chick little chick did you ruin the
小鸡鸡小鸡 你毁了
birthday cake no I didn't ruin the cake
小鸡小鸡小鸡 你毁了生日蛋糕 不,我没有毁了蛋糕
生日蛋糕 不,我没有毁了蛋糕
birthday cake no I didn't ruin the cake
Li
生日蛋糕 不,我没有毁了蛋糕李丽
lie it's so tickly so it was
谎言是如此滴滴滴滴滴滴滴的
you it really wasn't me let me tell you
说谎很痒,所以是你 真的不是我告诉你
oops oh no what do I
哦,哦,不,我该怎么办
do it got a little squished but I fixed
做它得到得到 有点压压碎,但我修了
it truth
做它得到得到 有点压碎 但我纠正了事实
事实真相
it truth
Tru
真理四号,真理四号,
特鲁鲁特
Tru
oh wow
楚啊哇哇
哦哇哇哦
oh wow
wow looks like she's telling the
哇 哇 哇 看起来她好像在说
哇,看起来她好像在说
wow looks like she's telling the
truth I'll go next okay let her try
真相,我接着去,让她试试
it got
真相,我接下来就去 好让她试一下
it tell them I didn't eat the cake
告诉他们我没吃蛋糕
muh fly
muh 苍蝇
fly it was you no way it wasn't me wait
飞飞的是你 绝对不可能 不是我在等
I remember
你飞飞飞,那绝对不是你,那不是我等我,我记得
now wow it's a
哇,现在哇,这是一个
cake no it's little rabbit's birthday
今天是小兔子生日
cake I can't eat it
小兔子的生日蛋糕,我不能吃
yet yes I can have these now
不过是的,我现在可以吃这个了
so I only ate the cupcakes next to it TR
所以我只吃了旁边的纸杯蛋糕 TR
TR sister monkey didn't ruin the cake
所以我只吃了旁边的纸杯蛋糕 猴子妹没把蛋糕弄坏
either then who could it
要么谁能做到呢?
be oh brother
要么是谁呢? 哦,兄弟
做为兄弟
be oh brother
rabbit did you touch the
哦,兄弟兔子,你有没有碰过
你碰过兔子吗?
rabbit did you touch the
cake I
兔子,你碰过蛋糕吗?
蛋糕一
cake I
didn't it can't be him
蛋糕,不是我做的,不可能是他
brother tell the Hat
哥哥跟海帽子说
yourself
哥哥,你自己跟帽子自己说
亲 亲
yourself
uh well I took just one
好,我只吃了一个
bite fly
咬牙苍蝇
fly I took two
我拍了两个
bites f
我咬了两只苍蝇 f
咬 咬 咬 f
bites f
f okay I took three
我拿了三个
f还好,我拿了三个
f okay I took three
B all my
我拿了三块B全拿了
B所有我
B all my
please stop I'll tell the
我所有的B,请停止,我会告诉
请你住手,我会告诉
please stop I'll tell the
truth I took just one fight at first but
请你住手,我会说实话,我刚开始只打了一仗,但...
一开始我只打了一仗
truth I took just one fight at first but
it was so
真相,我刚开始只打了一拳,但真的
确实如此
it was so
delicious I couldn't stop
太好吃了,我停不下来
eating
进食
wow I was afraid of getting caught so I
哇,我怕被抓到,所以我
covered it
哇,我怕被抓到,所以我盖了起来
up so that's what happened
所以事情就是这样
sorry little sister I shouldn't have
所以这就是发生的事情 对不起,小妹妹,我不应该有
对不起妹妹,我不应该有
sorry little sister I shouldn't have
done
对不起妹妹,我不应该做
已完成完成完成完成完成完成完成完成完成
done
that everyone does something wrong as
每个人都做错事
long as you try to fix things right it
人人都做错事 只要你试着纠正错误
只要你试着把事情解决好
long as you try to fix things right it
will be all
只要你试着把事情解决好 一切都会
将全部
will be all
right fix things right that's what the
一切都会好起来的 修复事情的权利 这就是
右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右右
right fix things right that's what the
kids
右右对右 纠正事情正确 这就是孩子们
儿 童 儿 童
kids
do I got
我有孩子吗? 我有孩子吗?
我做的,我有
do I got
it little sister let me make another
小妹妹让我再做一个
cake for you okay we'll help you uhh
小妹妹让我再给你做一个蛋糕 好,我们会帮你的
smells
闻闻气味
great Sheriff's knows things to keep in
伟大的郡长知道事情要坚持下去
mind kids if you make a mistake be brave
如果你犯错的话,孩子就会心怀勇气
and admit it don't tell eyes everyone
如果你犯了错误 孩子们就当心孩子 勇敢的承认 承认它不会告诉大家
并承认它不告诉眼睛 每个人
and admit it don't tell eyes everyone
does something wrong but as long as you
并承认它不告诉眼睛的眼睛 每个人做错事 但只要你
做错事,但只要你
does something wrong but as long as you
admit it and fix things right it will be
做错事,但只要你承认 和纠正事情,它会是
你们应当入其中,应当加以修补,应当加以修补,
admit it and fix things right it will be
all right please remember
承认它,修好它 一切都会好起来的 请记住
好吧,请记住
all right please remember
that always use a car
总是用汽车
seat I'm going to the amusement
座位,我要去娱乐
park sweetie don't climb up high you
甜心别爬高,别爬高
should walk
甜心别爬高,你该走
carefully Daddy I don't want to sit in
爸爸,小心,爸爸,我不想坐在这里
the car seat sweetie you should it will
爹地,我可不想坐在车座的座位上 甜心,如果可以的话
汽车座椅小甜甜,你应该会的
the car seat sweetie you should it will
keep you
汽车的座椅小甜甜,如果它能留住你
保留您
keep you
safe buckle up let's go
系好安全带,走吧
you can sit
您可以坐下
here I can't see anything
我在这里什么都看不见
Daddy it's all
爸爸,这是所有
done thank you so
非常感谢你们,感谢你们
much bye-bye
再见
by woof hi I'm Sheriff Labrador Sheriff
拜拜 拜拜 嗨 我是拉布拉多警长
我是拉布拉多警长
by woof hi I'm Sheriff Labrador Sheriff
Labrador my son was just in the car and
我是拉布拉多警长 拉布拉多警长 我儿子刚刚在车里
拉布拉多 我儿子刚刚在车里
Labrador my son was just in the car and
suddenly disappeared please
拉布拉多 我儿子刚刚在车里 突然失踪了
突然失踪 请立刻失踪
suddenly disappeared please
help we'll be right
突然消失 请帮帮忙 我们会是对的
帮我们做对了
help we'll be right
there Sheriff
在那里,警长
Labrador don't worry let us check
拉布拉多警长 别担心 让我们检查一下
first ah looks like he wasn't sitting in
首先啊 看来他没坐进去
his car seat Mr gecko did anything
首先啊 看起来他没有坐在车座上 壁虎先生做了什么事
壁虎先生做任何事情
his car seat Mr gecko did anything
unusual happen while you were
Gecko先生做任何事情 不寻常的事情发生 当你在
在你出生时 发生不寻常的不寻常情况
unusual happen while you were
driving yes a piece of newspaper blocked
在你开车时发生了不寻常的事 是的,有份报纸被封住
是的,是的,驾驶 一块报纸封住
driving yes a piece of newspaper blocked
my view so I had to make a sharp turn it
是的,是的,驾驶 一块报纸 封住我的观点 所以我不得不做一个尖锐的转弯
我的观点,所以我不得不 使它迅速转变
my view so I had to make a sharp turn it
seems like little gecko was thrown out
我的观点,所以我不得不做一个快速的转弯 它似乎像小壁虎被扔了出来
好像小壁虎被赶出去了
seems like little gecko was thrown out
of the car because he wasn't sitting in
好像小壁虎被从车里扔了出来 因为他没有坐在车里
因为他没有坐在车里
of the car because he wasn't sitting in
his car
因为他没有坐在车里
他的汽车
his car
seat let's go find him
他的车座,我们去找他
now my arm
现在我的手臂
hurts Daddy
现在我的手臂伤了爸爸
daddy where are
爸爸现在在哪里
you papion search with your super flying
你用你的超级飞翔搜索
eye got
你用你的超级飞的眼睛 寻找猎物
it little gecko where are
它的小壁虎在哪里
you I found a cushion on the ground
我在地上找到了一个垫子
ahead let's
我在前面的地上找到了一个垫子 让我们
向前走,让我们
ahead let's
go I think this is little gecko's
我想这是小壁虎的
cushion
我想这是小壁虎的坐垫
衬垫垫
cushion
ah and these are his
这些是他的
Footprints let's follow
脚印,我们跟着
them what should I do somebody help
我该做什么? 谁来帮帮忙?
me ouch
抚摸我 抚摸我
H my
我的爱啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊
H 我 我 的
H my
hat
帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子,帽子
help Target disappeared huh the
帮助目标失踪
footprint stopped let's see if he's
目标失踪了 足迹停止了 让我们看看他是不是
脚脚停了,看看他是不是
footprint stopped let's see if he's
nearby H what's
脚印停止了 让我们看看他是不是在H附近
附近H什么
nearby H what's
that error error returning
H附近地区错误返回时的错误错误是什么
now it's little gecko's hat oh no he
现在这是小壁虎的帽子 哦,不,他
might have fallen on that van ahead
不,他可能掉在前面的货车上
可能掉在前面的货车上
might have fallen on that van ahead
hurry Doby leave it to
可能已经跌倒在 面包车前 匆匆,多比离开它
赶快,多多快,留给
hurry Doby leave it to
me look it's little
我看起来还很小
gecko help
Gecko 壁壁帮助
H little
哈小,小小,小
gecko Sheriff
壁虎警长
labador everything's fine now always sit
壁虎警长拉卡多尔,一切都很好 现在总是坐着
拉玛多,一切都很好,现在总是坐着
labador everything's fine now always sit
in your car seat when riding in a car
现在一切都很好了 坐在你的车座上坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着
乘坐汽车时坐在汽车座椅上
in your car seat when riding in a car
okay uhhuh I got
坐在你的车座上 坐在你的车座上
it Sheriff labrador's safety talk
是拉布拉多警长的安全谈话
kids you should always sit in your car
拉布拉多警长的安全谈话 孩子们你应该永远坐在车里
孩子,你应该一直坐在车里
kids you should always sit in your car
seat when riding in a car car seats can
孩子你应该总是坐在你的汽车座椅上 当坐在汽车座上坐着汽车时
坐在车座上坐着汽车时可以坐的座椅
seat when riding in a car car seats can
protect you when the car suddenly stops
坐在车厢的座椅上 汽车的座椅可以保护你 当汽车突然停下时
当汽车突然停车时保护您
protect you when the car suddenly stops
or when there is an
当汽车突然停下或出现
或当存在
or when there is an
accident can you remember
或当发生意外时,你能记得
你还记得意外事故吗?
accident can you remember
that graffiti pranks are
涂鸦恶作剧
dangerous hello everyone Super Singer
大家好 超级歌手
peepy rabbit is here
大家好,大家好 超级歌手小兔子来了
AIT
出 约 约 约
music let's
AIT音乐,让我们
音乐 让我们
music let's
go PP rabbit PP rabbit loves to sing
音乐 让我们去PP兔子PP兔子 兔子喜欢唱歌
{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad0\3aHBE\4aH00\fscx67\fscy66\2cHFFFFFF\3cH2F2F2F) {\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad0\3aHBE\4aH00\fscx67\fscy66\2cHFFFFFF\3cH6F2F2F
go PP rabbit PP rabbit loves to sing
loves to sing everybody likes it
{\fn黑体\fs22\bord1\shad0\3aHBE\4aH00\fscx67\fscy66\2cHFFFFFF\3cH6C00\fscx67\fscy66\2cHFFFFFF\3cH2F2F2F) {\fn黑体\fs22\bord1\shad0\3aHBE\4aH00\fscx67\fscy66\2cHFFFFFF\3cH6F2F2F)
爱歌唱 每个人都喜欢
loves to sing everybody likes it
everybody likes it sing with me sing
爱唱歌 每个人都喜欢 每个人都喜欢它 喜欢它 和我一起唱 和我一起唱
每个人都喜欢它 和我一起歌唱
everybody likes it sing with me sing
with me thank
每个人都喜欢它 和我一起唱 和我一起唱 谢谢
you who where's everyone
你在哪里的每个人
W awesome Mr Mr
你在哪里,每个人都在哪里 W真棒先生先生
先生,你真棒,先生
W awesome Mr Mr
amazing my whole audience left me for
了不起先生 了不起先生 我的观众留给我
you what's so great about
# 你为何如此伟大 # # # 你为何如此伟大 # # # 你为何如此伟大 #
graffiti
涂鸦
yeah wow
涂鸦啊哇哇哇哇哇
呀哇哇哇哇
yeah wow
great o
哇哇伟大的O
大奥
great o
yeah Mr y amazing Mr
了不起的先生 令人惊叹的先生
先生 令人惊异的先生 先生
yeah Mr y amazing Mr
you like it that much
你那么喜欢它
huh then I will show you my
你那么喜欢它,那么,呵呵,然后我会 给你看我的
那样的话,我将使你看见我
graffiti who did this
是谁做的涂鸦
hit spray spray and
喷雾喷雾喷雾和
spray I can't hold it anymore it's a
喷雾我忍不住了,它是一个
bathroom ouch
洗手间和洗手间
paint it's just a painting what kids
它只是一幅绘画 什么孩子的绘画
let's go
绘画只是一幅画 孩子们让我们去画画
downstairs watch
楼下看着
out hey
楼下,小心,嘿嘿
papion clean up the graffiti on the sign
Papion 清理标牌上的涂鸦
got
清理标牌上的涂鸦
it this is a warning sign of a slippery
这确是一个警告的迹象,它确是滑的,
Road oh no who paint it over the warning
这是一条滑滑路的警告标志 哦,谁把它涂在警告上面呢?
哦,没有路啊,没有谁把它画在警告上面的
Road oh no who paint it over the warning
sign ouch my bottom Sheriff Labrador
哦,没有谁在警告牌上画它 触摸我的底部警长拉布拉多
触摸我的底部 警长拉布拉多
sign ouch my bottom Sheriff Labrador
please find out who did this leave it to
拉布拉多警长 请查清楚是谁干的
请查查是谁干的 交给谁了
please find out who did this leave it to
us ouch something's wrong over there
请查清楚是谁干的 这件事留给我们处理 那边出了点问题
我们摸着有问题的东西 那边有问题
us ouch something's wrong over there
let's
我们摸着东西出了问题,我们到那边去
让我们来
let's
go a a
来,我们来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来
girl oh my I'm going to be
女孩哦,我的 我将要是
late who did this it's horrible my
哦,女孩哦,我的 我要迟到了 谁做这 太可怕了,我的
这么晚了又是谁干的? 太可怕了,我的
late who did this it's horrible my
clothes got dirty too this kind of
我的衣服太脏了,太脏了
衣服太脏了 这种衣服太脏了
clothes got dirty too this kind of
graffiti is
衣服脏得也脏了 这种涂鸦是
涂鸦是
graffiti is
dangerous there's more over there papion
涂鸦是危险的 那边还有更多Papion
那边有危险,有危险,有危险,有危险,有危险,有危险,有危险,有危险,有危险,有危险,有危险,有危险,有危险,有危险,有危险,有危险,有危险,有危险,有危险,有危险,有危险
dangerous there's more over there papion
take charge here Toby let's keep
危险危险,那边还有更多 皮皮龙接管这里 托比,我们继续吧
investigating there's some here and here
调查中,这里和这里都有
too let's follow the graffiti
我们跟着涂鸦走
也跟着涂鸦走
too let's follow the graffiti
well done hey Cabot move back a bit I
做得好 嘿 Cabot 退后一点
want to enjoy my
做得好 嘿 Cabot 后退一点 我想好好享受
想要享受我
want to enjoy my
work isn't he cool
工作不是很酷吗?
what's going
发生什么事了
on ouch
触摸在触摸中
ouch r
头 脚 个 个 个 个 个 个 个 个 个 个 个 个 个 个 个 个 个 个 个 个 个 个 个 个 个 个 个 个 个
a there's graffiti ahead H looks like
前面有涂鸦 H看起来像
they did it oh
前面有涂鸦 H 看起来像是他们做的哦
他们做到了哦
they did it oh
no that
哦,不,他们做到了,哦,不,
否无
no that
hurt which way should we
那末,我们究竟应当崇拜哪条道路呢?
我们该用哪条路去伤人呢?
hurt which way should we
go this
我们该走哪条路? 走哪条路?
上这个
go this
way oh they're heading to the
朝这边走 哦,他们正朝
哦,他们正在前往
way oh they're heading to the
construction site what that's so
他们正前往建筑工地
建筑工地
construction site what that's so
dangerous let's go
建筑工地 那太危险了 我们走吧
hurry
快点
inside why are we at a construction site
为什么我们在建筑工地
let's get out of
我们出去吧
here that was so
在这里,这是如此
scary look this is a no entry sign you
吓吓吓你看,这是没有输入符号的你
were in danger because you painted over
吓吓吓吓吓你看,这是没有进入标志 你当时有危险,因为你画了画
因为你的涂漆而处于危险之中
were in danger because you painted over
the sign don't do that again okay
你画在牌子上,你才有危险 别再这样了,好吗?
牌子再不要这样了,好吗?
the sign don't do that again okay
I'll never do it
牌子再不要这样了 好,我永远不会做
我绝不会做
I'll never do it
again Sheriff labrador's safety
拉布拉多警长的安全
talk kids you shouldn't do graffiti in
拉布拉多警长的安全谈话 孩子们,你不应该做涂鸦
和孩子聊天,你不应该在
talk kids you shouldn't do graffiti in
public places it's not good and is
谈论孩子你不应该在公共场所 涂鸦,这是不好的,是
公共场所 不好 和是
public places it's not good and is
usually against the law for example if
公共公共场所不好,通常违法,例如
通常违法法律,例如:
usually against the law for example if
an important sign is covered by graffiti
通常违法,例如,如果一个重要标志被涂鸦覆盖
一个重要标志被涂鸦覆盖
an important sign is covered by graffiti
people might get in trouble or get
一个重要标志被涂鸦覆盖 人们可能陷入麻烦或获得
人们可能会陷入麻烦或陷入困境
people might get in trouble or get
hurt remember never do graffiti in
记住永远不要在
记住不要涂鸦
hurt remember never do graffiti in
public places
永远不要在公共场所涂鸦
peee rabbit got a
一只小兔子有一只小兔子
sunburn the sunlight is
太阳晒晒阳光
strong be careful not to get a sunburn
太阳晒太阳晒太阳 太阳晒太阳晒太阳 一定要小心不要晒太阳晒太阳
强健要小心不要晒晒太阳
strong be careful not to get a sunburn
Tada sir I'm all prepared wow so much
小心别晒晒晒晒伤 先生,我准备好了
塔达先生,我准备好了,哇,太厉害了
Tada sir I'm all prepared wow so much
sunscreen
塔达先生,我准备好了 哇,这么多防晒霜
oh
哦
no wait Beach here I
不等海滩在这里,我在这里
come
来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来
whoops
呼呼( 呼呼)
sweetie remember to put on sunscreen
亲爱的 记得放防晒霜
小甜甜记得涂防晒霜
sweetie remember to put on sunscreen
first okay
小甜甜记得先涂防晒霜
第一次还好
first okay
no it's
不,这是
icky piy rabbit you have to put it on or
不,这是舔皮兔 你必须穿上它,或
你一定要穿上它,还是要穿上它?
icky piy rabbit you have to put it on or
you'll get
你穿上它,不然你会得到
你会得到
you'll get
sunburned that's right we all
晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒晒
did I'm not afraid of the sun let's go
我不怕太阳,我们走吧
play hiy rabbit wait
我不怕太阳,我们去玩小兔子等
ouch my arm sting a little
摸摸我的手臂 有点刺痛
bit all time all time
所有时间的位数
coming
即将到来
he ouch it hurts feels like my Skin's
感觉就像我的皮肤
burning is it too hot today
感觉好像我的皮肤烧焦了 今天太热了
今天烧的太热了吗?
burning is it too hot today
H py rabbit you what's
白兔,你是什么
up
小兔子,你怎么样?
上上
up
huh how did this
怎么会这样?
happen huh why are you all
你们为什么都这样?
okay because we've put on
为什么你们都没事 因为我们穿上了
sunscreen and how come you're all fine
防晒霜和你们怎么都没事
we are robots no need for
防晒霜和为什么你们都没事 我们都是不需要的机器人
sunscreen right
右侧防晒霜
keep keep ouch it
防晒霜右手伸直
hurts stay away from
远离伤害
me I got
离我远点,我得到
我得到我,我得到
me I got
sunburned I need to go back it's so
我被晒伤了,我需要回去
hot my hand
热热的我的手
oh
哦
hey if I follow the cloud Shadow I'll be
如果我跟着阴云的阴影,我会是
okay oh
还好哦
no wao the sand is burning
沙沙正在燃烧
沙沙在燃烧
no wao the sand is burning
hot I can walk in his
没有沙沙在烧热,我可以走进他的
shadow all right let me warm up first
先让我暖暖身吧
right
让我先热热一下
右右右右右
right
left stretching
右左伸展
the sunlight ice cream ice
阳光的冰淇淋冰
cream oh the ice cream truck I'll go
阳光阳光 冰淇淋冰淇淋 哦 冰淇淋卡车 我去
奶油冰淇淋卡车 我去
cream oh the ice cream truck I'll go
hide over
冰淇淋卡车我躲起来
there with air conditioning much
那里有很多空调
better
更好
thanks don't move away
谢谢,不要走开
looks like he got sunburned let's go
他好像被晒晒晒伤了 走吧
check on him
他好像被晒晒伤了,我们去看看他
检查他
check on him
okay no way this is the wrong
绝对不行,这是不对的
direction what do I do oh parasols oh
这方向不对,我该做什么? 哦,哦,哦,哦!
我该做什么? 哦! 阳伞! 哦!
direction what do I do oh parasols oh
thank
我该怎么办? 哦,阳伞哦,谢谢
感谢感谢 感谢 感谢 感谢
thank
goodness he's over there
谢天谢地,他在那边
good swimming will be faster
好游泳会更快
okay Yik my skin so
好,好,好,好,我皮肤这样
sore
疼痛
ouch I can't
# 我无法 # # Auch I can't #
swim
我无法游泳
help oh no he's in danger
哦,不,不,不,他有危险
Doby
多比
coming sir take
来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来 来来来来来来来来来来来来来来 来来来来来来来来来来来来来
it he's sunburn take him to the hospital
他晒伤了,就送他去医院
Sheriff labrador's safety
拉布拉多警长的安全
talk kids if you stay in the sun too
拉布拉多警长的安全谈话 孩子们,如果你也呆在阳光下
如果你也待在阳光下 和孩子聊天
talk kids if you stay in the sun too
long it can burn your skin even making
如果你在太阳下呆太久,会和孩子聊天, 甚至会烧伤你的皮肤,甚至会烧伤你的皮肤
长长长的皮肤,甚至可以烧灼你的皮肤
long it can burn your skin even making
it red and
长长的皮肤可以燃烧 甚至使皮肤红,
红色和红色
it red and
flister so when you play outside make
红红的,盛红的,所以当你在外面玩的时候
当你在户外玩时
flister so when you play outside make
sure to put on sunscreen to protect
当你在外面玩的时候 一定要戴上防晒霜来保护
yourself that's how we can prevent
这就是我们如何防止
sunburns
这样我们才能避免晒伤
W revolving door
W 旋转门
safety there have been many thefts in
安全安全区发生了多起盗窃事件
the mall lately we need to find the
安全安全在商场里 发生了许多盗窃案 最近我们需要找到
商场最近我们需要找到
the mall lately we need to find the
Thief
商场最近我们需要找到盗贼
okay my car watch
OK我的车表
out be careful when you go through a
当你经历一个时,要小心
evolving door or you might get
当你穿过进进进出门时要小心,或者你可能会得到
或你可能会得到
evolving door or you might get
hurt sweetie how did you end up here
进化门 或者你可能会受伤 亲爱的 你是怎么到这里的
亲爱的,你怎么会到这儿来?
hurt sweetie how did you end up here
while I wasn't looking Mr Yak it's very
亲爱的,你怎么会跑到这儿来? 我当时没看亚克先生
当我不看亚克先生的时候
while I wasn't looking Mr Yak it's very
dangerous for kids to go through a
当我没看亚克先生的时候 孩子们要经历一个非常危险的
(a) 使儿童经受危险
dangerous for kids to go through a
revolving door alone okay I'll keep that
孩子们独自穿过旋转门很危险 好吧,我留着
独自一人的旋转门 好,我留着这个
revolving door alone okay I'll keep that
in mind here your car thank
独自一人的旋转门,好吗 好吧,我会记住,在这里,你的车在这里,谢谢。
记住你的车,谢谢
in mind here your car thank
you see you later good thing you didn't
你的车在这里,你的心意 在这里,你的车在这里,谢谢你,谢谢你看到你 以后的好东西,你没有
看到你以后看到你 幸好你没有
you see you later good thing you didn't
get hurt it's all my fault I'll buy you
以后再看你,好在你没受伤 都是我的错,我买给你
受伤都是我的错,我买给你
get hurt it's all my fault I'll buy you
another balloon
受伤都是我的错,我再给你买一个气球
另一个气球
another balloon
yay W oh oh where's my
又一个气球 yay W oh oh 哪里是我的
呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀我的
yay W oh oh where's my
wallet oh no my wallet is
我的钱包呢? 哦,我的钱包呢? 哦,我的钱包呢?
钱包哦,没有我的钱包是
wallet oh no my wallet is
missing balloon balloon where's my
钱包哦,没有我的钱包 缺少气球气球 气球,哪里是我的
失踪的气球气球气球 哪里是我的
missing balloon balloon where's my
wallet Grandma I want a balloon qu my
不见了气球气球 哪里是我的钱包 奶奶 我想要一个气球
奶奶钱包 我想要一个气球
wallet Grandma I want a balloon qu my
wallet is missing huh qu what happened
奶奶钱包 我想要一个气球 QQ气球 我的钱包不见了 哈哈 QQ 发生了什么事
钱包不见了,哈 ququ 发生了什么事
wallet is missing huh qu what happened
Sheriff Labrador someone stole my wallet
拉布拉多警长发生的事 有人偷了我的钱包
拉布拉多警长 有人偷了我的钱包
Sheriff Labrador someone stole my wallet
qu what the thief is back let's go find
拉布拉多警长 有人偷了我的钱包
贼回来了,我们去找
qu what the thief is back let's go find
out who did it now got
贼回来后,我们去查清楚是谁干的
是谁做的,现在谁得到了
out who did it now got
it he looks
他看着
suspicious it must be
他看起来可疑 一定是
一定是可疑的
suspicious it must be
him daddy bought something for
一定是他怀疑爸爸买了些东西
爸爸买东西给他
him daddy bought something for
you a
爸爸给你买了点东西
sir I didn't see anyone suspicious the
先生,我没有看到任何人怀疑
thief might have already left well
先生,我没有看到任何人怀疑 小偷可能已经走了
小偷可能已经走了
thief might have already left well
there's something suspicious about
盗贼可能已经走了 有一些可疑的东西
有可疑的东西
there's something suspicious about
weasel
黄鼠狼有可疑之处
wow I got
哇,我得到了
it where's my
# 在那里是我的爱 # # # 在那里是我的爱 # # # #
wallet let's
我的钱包在哪里?
钱包,让我们来
wallet let's
go you stole this wallet didn't you oh
钱包,我们走吧,你偷了这个钱包
你偷了这个钱包,不是吗?
go you stole this wallet didn't you oh
it's the
你偷了这个钱包,不是吗? 哦,这是
这是
it's the
police I can't find my wallet
是警察,我找不到我的钱包
警察,我找不到我的钱包
police I can't find my wallet
either you stole it right no it wasn't
警察,我找不到我的钱包 也找不到我的钱包 你偷对了,不,它不是
要么你偷对了 要么你偷对了 不 不 不是的
either you stole it right no it wasn't
me this is my own wallet
不是,不是我,这是我自己的钱包
这是我自己的钱包
me this is my own wallet
huh he's right this is his
这是我自己的钱包,他说得对,这是他的
他说得对,这是他的
huh he's right this is his
wallet
钱包钱包
wait Sheriff
等待警督的钱包
等警长
wait Sheriff
Labrador what's
等待拉布拉多警长什么
拉布拉多是什么
Labrador what's
wrong your shoelace it's loose ah
拉布拉多,什么是错的 你的鞋带松了啊
弄错鞋带了 松了啊
wrong your shoelace it's loose ah
oh it's my
弄错你的鞋带了 松松了啊哦 这是我的
哦,这是我的
oh it's my
wallet oh no they got me it was you
哦,这是我的钱包 哦,不,不,不,他们得到了我 是你
钱包哦,不,他们得到了我 是你
wallet oh no they got me it was you
Thief I got to
钱包啊,不不,他们抓着我了 是你小偷,我不得不
小偷,我必须
Thief I got to
run stop right there stop you won't
小偷,我必须跑 停下来,站在那里 停下来,你不会的
跑停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停
run stop right there stop you won't
catch
跑停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停
me it's
我,这是
stinks bye-bye
臭臭的拜拜
oh why did I turn back you can't run
臭臭的拜拜 哦,为什么我转回去,你跑不跑
away hurry he went into the clothing
快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快,他穿衣服,穿衣服,穿衣服,穿衣服,穿衣服,穿衣服,穿衣服,穿衣服,
shop over
匆匆忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙,他忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去到他忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙忙
there that's strange where did he go
奇怪,他去了哪里? 哪里? ? ?
let's check the fitting
奇怪,他去了哪里? 检查一下装配
rooms no one's here
客房没人在这里
here sir what did I do I'm sorry we've
先生,我做了什么对不起我们
got the wrong
先生,我做了什么? 对不起,我们搞错了
person the last
最后一个人
room he must be in
他必须住的最后一间房里的人
他一定在房间里
room he must be in
here what are you doing here you scared
他一定在房间里 你在这里做什么 你害怕
你在这里做什么 你害怕
here what are you doing here you scared
me I'm sorry
你在这里做什么 你吓吓我 对不起
对不起,对不起
me I'm sorry
where's
对不起,我... ... 对不起,我...
Weasel oh no these are weasel's clothes
黄鼠狼哦,不,这些是黄鼠狼的衣服
what then that lady was weasel in
哦,不,这些是黄鼠狼的衣服 然后那位女士是黄鼠狼
然后那个女人又在
what then that lady was weasel in
Disguise let's get
然后这位女士在假扮中 是个黄鼠狼,让我们得到
变形 让我们开始吧
Disguise let's get
him there he is they found
他在那里,他在那里,他在那里,他在那里,他们发现,
me hurry
他在那里,他在那里,他们发现我快,快
快点
me hurry
hurry hurry hurry stop it's dangerous to
快点快点快快快快快 停止危险
快点快点快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快
hurry hurry hurry stop it's dangerous to
do that I'm not listening to
快点快点快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快
做我听不听的
do that I'm not listening to
you my tail it hurts so
尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾尾
much that was so scary you shouldn't
如此可怕,你不应该
steal f
太可怕了,你不该偷的f
偷窃 f
steal f
you're coming with
偷你来
us Sheriff labrador's safety
我们拉布拉多警长的安全
talk kids you need to stay close to your
我们拉布拉多警长的安全谈话 孩子们,你需要跟紧你
和孩子说话,你需要跟紧你
talk kids you need to stay close to your
parents when going through revolving
儿童在旋转时要跟父母亲亲亲亲近
父母在循环中
parents when going through revolving
doors keep the direction the door is
当父母穿过旋转门时 守住门的方向
门守着门的方向 门就是门
doors keep the direction the door is
turning don't push or try to squeeze in
门门保持方向 门正在转向 不要推或试图挤进去
转弯不要推 或试图挤进来
turning don't push or try to squeeze in
and don't play around or you might get
转弯不推不推 也不试图挤挤 和不玩耍 或你可能会得到
不要玩耍,或者你可能会得到
and don't play around or you might get
hurt in the case of an emergency press
并且不要玩耍 或你可能会受伤 在紧急情况下 记者
紧急情况下受伤的记者
hurt in the case of an emergency press
the emergency button to stop the door
遇紧急情况受伤时,按紧急按钮以停止门关
紧急按钮 停止门
the emergency button to stop the door
please remember these tips left
紧急按钮来停门 请记住左侧的提示
本字幕由AI大模型生成